export const exampleDecks = {    
  'German': {
    id: 'german',
    name: 'German',
    cards: [
      { question: 'Fish', answer: 'Fisch' },
      { question: 'Milk', answer: 'Milch' },
      { question: 'Eggs', answer: 'Eier' },
      { question: 'Cheese', answer: 'Kase' },
      { question: 'Butter', answer: 'Butter' },
      { question: 'Bread', answer: 'Brot' },
    ]
  },
  'Spanish': {
    id: 'spanish',
    name: 'Spanish',
    cards: [
      { question: 'Fish', answer: 'Pez' },
      { question: 'Milk', answer: 'Leche' },
      { question: 'Eggs', answer: 'Hoevos' },
      { question: 'Cheese', answer: 'Queso' },
      { question: 'Butter', answer: 'Mantequilla' },
      { question: 'Bread', answer: 'Pan' },
    ]
  },
}